She's Out There Somewhere… Finding Her is the Hard Part!
In Search of… the Perfect "10" is a comedy film directed by Gregory Dark.
Host Andy Nichols and his trusty Mam-O-Reader scanner searches Hollywood to find the perfect
breasts, and several gorgeous women are willing to bare all in order to win.
Farley Buxton, played by Andy Nichols.
Roxanne Dieselberger - Perfect Girl #10, played by Michelle Bauer.
Dr. Titzling, played by Jack Baker.
Perfect Girl #3, played by Blondi.
Perfect Girl #9, played by Terri Lynn Peake.
Perfect Girl #5, played by Gail Harris.
Leonard Simon Nimoy ( NEE-moy; March 26, 1931 – February 27, 2015) was an American actor and
director, famous for playing Spock in the Star Trek franchise for almost 50 years.
This includes originating Spock in the original Star Trek series in 1966, then Star Trek: The Animated Series, the first
six Star Trek films, Star Trek: The Next Generation, the 2009 Star Trek film, and Star Trek Into Darkness.
Nimoy also directed films, including Star Trek III: The Search for Spock (1984), Star Trek IV: The Voyage Home
(1986), and Three Men and a Baby (1987), and his career included roles in music videos and video games.
In addition to acting and filmmaking, Nimoy was a
photographer, author, singer, and songwriter.
Nimoy's acting career began during his early twenties, teaching acting classes in
Hollywood and making minor film and television appearances throughout the 1950s.
From 1953 to 1955, he served in the United States Army as a sergeant in the
Special Services, an entertainment branch of the American military.
He originated and developed Spock beginning with the 1964 Star Trek television pilot "The Cage" and 1965’s "Where No Man Has Gone
Before", through series' end in early 1969, followed by eight feature films and guest appearances in spin-offs.
From 1967 to 1970, Nimoy had a music career with Dot Records,
with his first and second albums mostly as Spock.
After the original Star Trek series, Nimoy starred in Mission: Impossible for two seasons, hosted the documentary
series In Search of..., appeared in Columbo, and made several well-received stage appearances.
Nimoy's portrayal of Spock made a significant cultural impact
and earned him three Emmy Award nominations.
His public profile as Spock was so strong that both his autobiographies, I Am Not Spock (1975) and I
Am Spock (1995), were written from the viewpoint of coexistence with the character.
Leonard Nimoy played the elder Spock, with Zachary Quinto portraying a
younger Spock, in the 2009 Star Trek reboot film, directed by J.
In 2010, Nimoy announced that he was retiring from playing Spock, citing both his advanced
age and the desire to give Quinto full media attention as the character.
His final role as Spock (and his final role overall) was in
the 2013 sequel, Star Trek Into Darkness.
Nimoy died in February 2015 after a long case of chronic
obstructive pulmonary disease (COPD).
His death was international news and was met with expressions of shock and grief by
fans, Star Trek co-stars, scientists, celebrities, and the media.
An asteroid was named 4864 Nimoy in his honor.
For the Love of Spock (2016) was produced by his son Adam about his life and career, and
Remembering Leonard Nimoy (2017) was produced by his daughter Julie about his illness.
The tone is lighthearted.